gordonandthewhale.com 2012-06-05

# Gordon and the Whale : Privacy Policy » GordonandtheWhale.com

**We are committed to protecting your privacy**

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect that information.

**Information Collected**

We may collect all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your email address, together with data about your use of the website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.

Additionally, your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files- “cookies” – that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired.

**Interaction with Children**

The [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/) governs information gathering online from or about children under the age of 13. Verifiable consent from a child's parent or guardian is required before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from a child under the age of 13.

We collect no information about you or your child, other than that detailed in the previous section, when you visit our web site unless you choose to provide information to us.

**Information Use**

We use the information collected primarily for demographics, traffic reports, and to provide additional services for which you have visited this site. Data collected within the US is held in accordance with the Data Protection Act. All reasonable precautions have been taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information.

**Disclosing Information**

We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.

We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties – for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.

**Third Party**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Public Forums**

This site provides and encourages interaction with its viewers with a third-party public forum. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. GordonandtheWhale.com cannot be held responsible in any way for any information posted or otherwise distributed by public users via its public commenting.

**Changes to this Policy**

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please feel free to [email ](mailto:contact@gordonandthewhale.com)us. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details form any list under our control.
